Congratulations,
Rin.
Actually...
I lied.
To tell you the truth...
I was scared.
I didn't know if I'd be
happy for you.
For you, and your child.
Every time you spoke about your baby,
you were clearly so happy.
And I knew I had to be happy for you, too.
But...
Some part of me
deep, deep inside my heart,
wanted to feel jealous.
I'm so sorry.
And yet.
Now that your baby is born,
and I see you'll become a mother,
I feel so relieved.
I feel so, so overjoyed.
I'm telling the truth.
I really am.
I think...
My body's circumstances
will always,
always bother me.
But...
I've decided not to let it shackle me.
Though it may take time,
I want to embrace the future.
Because you also made your dreams come true.
Thank you, Rin.
I have to go now.
I have someone I need to talk to.
Sui?
I need to ask you a question.
We have nothing to talk about.
I can't ever forgive you.
But my sister.
You found her when she had collapsed.
Didn't you?
A shame she had a successful delivery.
Thank you.
What?
I heard you helped her.
Now why would I do that?
My sister's husband told me
you had passed by.
Ugh...
Come on, get a grip.
I can't forgive you
for the harm you've done.
I most likely won't ever forgive you.
But I'm truly thankful you saved my sister,
and her baby.
Really, thank you.
You got the wrong person.
Takizawa.
You have hurt me, time and time again.
You have caused me great strife.
Even so, I can't change the fact
that I am infertile.
And though I try to accept this fact,
I can't help but feel like
I'm misfortunate at times.
Even so,
I want to become happy,
regardless of whether or not I can conceive.
Though I might not succeed immediately,
I want to learn to enjoy my life.
Takizawa.
Don't you also want to change?
It doesn't matter who you are.
Everyone has a shot at changing their future.
[Name: You]
What a pile.
Like you're one to talk.
That mountain of gifts
is all from you, isn't it?
You doting aunt.
Hey, it's not that bad.
Thanks for the presents, you two.
I won't have to go shopping for a while.
Glad we could help.
Sorry she chose to clonk out
at a really inopportune time.
Don't worry about it.
We're having fun just looking.
If anything, she's giving you a nice break.
- How filial of her.
- Yeah.
She's been such a good girl.
Something up?
Nothing, really.
I was just thinking back
to the day You was born.
Don't feel like you have to answer today.
Your offer is too generous.
I am happy you choose me.
Thank you.
Not at all.
If anything, I ought to be thanking you.
I respect you greatly, Sui.
As do I, Hirose.
I am truly grateful
for all you've given me.
And yet...
I don't think I am your ideal match.
I had earnestly considered
a future with you.
I'm certain it would be a happy one.
But I also felt as though
I would be taking advantage of you.
I had so readily assumed
no one would accept my body as is.
Which is why...
I had presumed on your kind heart.
You truly are an honest individual.
I am satisfied enough knowing if,
even for a moment, you chose to look my way.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
I must be slightly drunk.
Pardon?
You already have someone else in mind, no?
You'll do just fine, Monou.
After all, you're the woman I fell for.
Now, go on to them.
Hirose...
Thank you.
[LIBRARY]
Heading home? How about we...
Wait, I thought you just took the exam.
I probably failed,
so I'm studying for next year.
You're a hard worker.
I'm really not.
I just needed something else to focus on.
Huh?
It feels fulfilling to keep my mind busy.
Maybe it's good that I'm cultivating
my own happy space.
I see.
Well, good luck with your studies.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
How's the design coming along?
I'm almost done, thanks to you all.
I'm just finalizing some details.
Your worksheets helped
with my studies, as well.
I'm glad. Let's both give it our all, yeah?
Of course.
See you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Night.
Take care.
I wanted to give it my all, too.
But Nana doesn't need me around.
I thought you were more of a go-getter.
I've got a delicate heart, okay?
No, you're right.
Nana. I was thinking of heading out, too.
Sure. Let's go.
Take care, Mao.
Huh? Monou?
Good evening.
I thought you had the day off today.
I did.
I just forgot something at the office.
Must've been something important.
You could say that.
Well, hope you find it.
Shall we, Nana?
Right. Good night, Monou.
See you both tomorrow.
You forgot something?
I would've brought it over for you.
No, I lied.
What?
I love you, Mao.
Huh?
Sorry, that must've surprised you.
I just...
I really needed you to know, so...
Here I am.
Mao.
I decided I'd change.
Sorry.
I didn't realize you'd be busy.
I just really wanted you
to hear how I felt.
See you tomorrow.
Why would you get the jump on me?
Huh?
Come with me.
I broke up with Mizuno.
So, I was trying to focus on work,
and not romance.
But I want to change, too.
Mao?
I respect you, Sui.
I respect your efforts to try hard alone.
And yet...
I want to be someone you can rely on.
To be your support, when you're tired.
I want to hug you,
and tell you you're not alone.
I want to be the only one for you.
I love you, too.
Mao.
There's something I haven't told you yet.
What is it?
I'm infertile.
I want to stay with you, of course.
But if my infertility changes how you feel...
I love you, Sui.
Why would you push me away like that?
Don't assume I'd leave you.
I don't want you to worry
over nonexistent futures, alone.
Sorry.
I should have mentioned this earlier.
Sui.
I knew about your body,
before I fell for you.
You did?
I overheard someone mention it.
But that never bothered me.
I love you, for who you are.
Mao...
You never know how you'll feel in the future.
People change.
That goes for the both of us, right?
I'm just as anxious, you know.
You are?
How about this?
I decide my own happiness.
And you decide yours.
It's my choice?
Then we can think about our future, together.
I don't mind if we argue about it.
So long as we agree on the outcome.
Let's share both the good
and the bad with each other.
Yeah.
I want to consider a future with you.
Because I want us to be happy, together.
[3 Years Later]
[Idea Construction Office]
A dating app?
Can you blame a guy?
Waiting for a girl isn't getting me anywhere.
What if you get a successful match?
Then I'd take the girl out to dinner.
She'll get a free meal.
It's what a guy's gotta do
to get dinner with a girl.
Let me have my fun, okay?
You should just treat me to dinner instead.
Huh?
We could celebrate the fact
I'm a licensed architect now.
Or not, if you don't want to.
No, let's do this. Let's go.
Dinner?
Let me tag along.
- No!
What?
Look at me.
Daddy's taking a picture.
Say cheese!
Got it.
How do we look?
Let me see.
Nice picture!
Misaki, you've changed.
Really?
I think you're imagining things.
Hurry up. We still have stores to hit.
Wait up!
Jeez, buy a car already.
With my salary? Not happening.
Then get your daddy to retire already.
Not happening either!
Hey, wait!
Give this a once over.
Yes, sir.
Come over for dinner next Saturday.
My relatives sent too many vegetables, again.
Still working?
I didn't realize what time it was.
I'll wait until you're at
a good stopping point.
Matsubara brought us souvenirs.
He wished you luck on the contest.
He's a considerate guy, isn't he?
- Yum.
- Yeah, that's good.
Wonder where this is from.
[Mao Tsukidome Architects]
What should we make for dinner?
Hot pot.
Hot pot?
Sounds good, actually.